4/6/2021 Rilwan

# Yusuf Rilwan



Software Developer

A full stack developer with hands-on experience designing, developing, and implementing web applications. I develop responsive and performant web applications with variety of development languages and modern technologies. I am dedicated and ready to learn new technologies as the project demands.

### Skills

HTML/CSS, Javascript [ES6], Bootstrap, Vue.js, Jquery, Git, EJS, Node.js, MongoDB, GraphQL, Netlify, Heroku, Search Engine Optimisation.

# Experience

HNG Internships - Frontend Developer [Intern]

MAY 2020 - AUGUST 2020

During the internship, I interacted and worked with lots of interns as a team. This Internship particularly helped me master the use of git and working as a team. I carried out the following activities,

- Worked with co-interns as a team and mastered the use of git
- Developed user interfaces with modern JavaScript frameworks, HTML5 and CSS3.
- Collaborated with product managers, testers, and developers to build responsive and performant websites
- Collaborated with a product designer to create a unique startup

Nigeria Television Authority - IT Officer [Intern]

MARCH 2018 - NOVEMBER 2018

During internship with the organization, I worked closely with my supervisor and co-interns to carry out various activities IT department

- · I deployed, configured, and maintained the organization ICT systems and databases for optimal performance
- I carried out weekly anti-virus updates for all the computers in the organization
- I was the go-to person for general repair and troubleshooting of hardware, operating systems, application and any ICT related activities
- I enhanced the organization IT system through appropriate upgrades

#### Education

Obafemi Awolowo Univeristy - BSc. Electronic and Electrical Engineering

2014 - 2019

## **Projects**

Chat App SVG Animator Ecoutez Music App Quiz App